comedian and podcaster Amanda seals
tortured Soul has revealed that her and
Issa Ray almost got into a physical
altercation which sparked the beginning
of the end of their relationship let's
get into it oh I forgot artist
intellectual she's a intellectual on
Instagram that's that's that's what her
claim of Fame is waiting to shoot and we
were chitchatting everybody together as
a group was all
chitchatting and we started talking
about this new show a new show had come
out okay and as we started talking about
the new show that come out Issa started
reing a uh reading a review of the show
out loud to the group okay she's reading
the show out loud to the group so we're
all sitting there listening and we're
all commenting and involved in the
commentary and in the conversation
everybody as a group is talking and when
I say everybody I mean the cast members
we're all chitchatting about it okay
together all of us together and she uh
fell off from the conversation because
she was reading the rest of the article
to herself so then she at the I guess
when she was done reading she said
oh yeah it ends with da d da da da and I
asked oh well did they mention da d da
da da and she said why don't you just
read it yourself
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh I mean I kind of feel Amanda on that
part like that would set me off if that
was the thing that uh was snap back at
me but you got to remember Amanda this
was your boss and I think she always
leaves that part out of the equation
right even though Issa is fun Issa is
Young she's still the executive producer
and producer of the show insecure mind
you she's talking about this several
years after the show's been off the air
so ask me why I have no idea but uh I
guess this is a fighter for her content
on her YouTube channel now since she's
lost a radio show don't I believe we
covered that but if you didn't know she
lost a radio show nationally syndicated
radio show um that she was doing and
she's become a YouTuber like us all all
roads you lead to YouTube but for her
still to be talking about this all these
years later must have really got under
his again da da da da and she said why
don't you just read it
yourself got a point
though sips or
[Music]
te and that was the last
day because I had taken so much stess
and weirdness for the past five seasons
and it was the last season and I just
said you know what I don't got to take
this no more
okay that's important it's the last
season I was wondering on what the
timeline was of this so this was the
last season got it just said you know
what I don't got to take this no
more I don't know who the you talking to
I don't know why you're even addressing
me this way we're in a whole group of
people together we're all discussing
this I'm actually showing interest and
so that was the last day and I have
never spoken to her
again because I'm always going to show
you respect unless you play me which I
have one time got out of my face because
I felt played and then she then tried to
act like she was gonna fight me when we
was on stage doing a read a a read about
a movie and I was like stop cuz you're
not we're not about to fight and then we
were able to have a civil conversation
after that listen she got in her
feelings fine fine fine fine you don't
know Issa might have been serious she
might have really wanted that fate fine
but trying to Sun me not trying sunning
me in front of everybody is unacceptable
for a number of reasons one sunning a
girl is
crazy getting suned as a girl is
crazy but she was the boss so she can
kind of do that with the authority that
she has um and obviously she's not
telling the whole story there must have
been something that frustrated Issa
along the way about Amanda cuz we we've
seen Amanda's character post insecure
and and prior to insecure believe it or
not and there are certain things that
Amanda does that are quite
annoying I am your
employee I'm your employee that's number
one I don't you're suning me for what
like I'm not it's not that I did
anything wrong it's not like you're
correcting me in the work two I am your
peer colleague and three I'm your Elder
she pulled the Elder card out oh
wow what she got to buy a couple years
how old is he s anamanda
43 it ain't not even like it's about
three years difference
um
Elder I think that's disrespectful to
call yourself her Elder and she's
literally like your boss she's like now
you going now make sure you remember you
I'm still your Elder I might only be
three years older than you and you might
be my boss and my and responsible for
how I get paid but don't you disrespect
your
elders boom boom boom so that was the
last day I'm not doing it I'm not gonna
keep putting up with this behavior I'm
not going to keep interacting with this
I'm not going to keep cow toeing I'm not
going to keep being the bigger person
who comes and tries to soothe and smooth
thing is cow Towing because you're the
boss I'm not GNA do it
you better if you want that Che the last
day so for anyone who's ever wanted to
know you just got a random tea that was
the last
day there we
go okay let's get back to
tenous tenebrous
yes that's a word of the day yeah I was
not tenous about my feelings moving
forward after that very clear very clear
so let's uh play something let's Okay so
that was interesting Amanda self-
diagnosed autistic let's never forget
that um I wonder if she had known she
was autistic at that point and not that
it really matters but the fact of the
matter is her and Issa Reay were not
getting along at the end of production
so this puts a lot of perspective on the
the Emy night party that she was
asked to leave when she was invited in
by somebody a guest and uh you know they
were talking about the beef with uh the
publicist that makes more sense now
because the publicist passed on word to
Issa come on Issa I mean passed on word
to Amanda come on Amanda you know what
it is right why you coming to issa's
party if you've almost got into a
physical altercation with her I wonder
or if you've had issues back and forth
cuz I don't think that had happened that
was before the last season I'm thinking
but you know what do y'all think are you
all on Amanda side with this is Amanda
was Issa Ray just tripping and out of
her mind to snap on Amanda or had there
been a buildup of time that happens on
set trust me I know people are friends
starting off you know cuz I you remember
Amanda was doing her own web series and
Issa produced her web series
that's how they initially had connection
right I guess Issa saw something in
Amanda like she's cool I would like to
work with her but somehow by the end of
that process and a whole another
show she's built up a different
relationship with Amanda or Amanda wore
on her nerves to a point where she was
about to put hands on her like you know
what it's the last
season yeah we gonna fight
you know like I can imagine that moment
man but let me know what y'all think
about it in the
comments uh is Amanda right or is Issa
probably right being the boss and being
the head of the show The Creative uh
leader of that program and is Amanda
even right to still be talking about
this all these years later insecure off
the air just leave the Legacy as it were
this Amanda does give give a clinic in
Burning Bridges in Hollywood let me just
say now she falls forward a lot of times
you know gets her own radio show she
goes on tour you know she does stand up
gets a special after all of
that but she
really has no regard for ever working
with Issa Reay again and that was kind
of her biggest break in Hollywood in
recent history so I wonder I wonder if
there's any way you can say Amanda was
right in that
situation um other than the fact that
she did get
disrespected well she got sunned she did
get sunned but either way let me know
what you think about it in the comments
if you like this video like comment
subscribe hit the Bell notification for
all uploads if you want to watch more
please watch one of these videos down
below make sure you sign up for faet
media.com fset mediad direct that is my
streaming service there get uncensored
content content you can't find on this
YouTube platform that I've done and also
a lot of new stuff that I'm cooking up
there's going to be live streams over
there occasionally and it's going to be
a lot of fun everything every one of
your subscriptions goes to support faet
media if I can get enough going over
there you might see a faet media movie
coming out of that so you see I'm
thinking in the future you know what I'm
saying trying to trying to use my Isa
brain not my Amanda the
brain but either way uh yeah this
is FAL media